[
  {
	"title": "Present Continuous 1",
	"description": "The following verbs are not normally used in the present continuous",
	"tasks": [
	  {
		"front": "like",
		"back": "find agreeable, enjoyable, or satisfactory",
		"ru": "нравиться",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "I <strong>like</strong> English, but I cannot speak well."
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "want",
		"back": "хотеть",
		"ru": "хотеть",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "need",
		"back": "нуждаться",
		"ru": "перевод",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "prefer",
		"back": "предпочитать",
		"ru": "предпочитать",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		  ]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "know",
		"back": "знать",
		"ru": "знать",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "realise",
		"back": "понимать, осознавать",
		"ru": "понимать, осознавать",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "suppose",
		"back": "= предполагать",
		"ru": "предполагать",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "mean",
		"back": "имею в виду, означать",
		"ru": "имею в виду, означать",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "understand",
		"back": "понимать",
		"ru": "понимать",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "believe",
		"back": "верить",
		"ru": "верить",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "remember",
		"back": "запомнить",
		"ru": "запомнить",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "belong",
		"back": "принадлежать",
		"ru": "принадлежать",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "fit",
		"back": "поместиться, подходить",
		"ru": "поместиться, подходить",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "contain",
		"back": "содержать",
		"ru": "содержать",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "consist",
		"back": "be composed or made up of",
		"ru": "состоять, совпадать",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "no example"
		]
	  },
	  {
		"front": "seem",
		"back": "казаться",
		"ru": "казаться",
		"tcr": "[ trænˈskrɪp.ʃən ]",
		"sound": "",
		"note": [
		  "She <strong>seemed</strong> happy enough.",
		  "It <strong>seemed</strong> like a good idea at the time.",
		  "There doesn't <strong>seem</strong> to be any real solution."
		]
	  }
	]
  }
]